uppic.mobi 2014-04-12

# Free Image Hosting By Uppic.Mobi CoverDD.com ฝากรูป ฝากปก ฝากแบบสกรีน CD DVD VCD MP3 Blu-Ray เกมส์ -

'This Site' is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information of individuals / users and/or companies who use our services.. 

**How we use your personal information**

We only use the personal information obtained from you to respond to, and process your request for our services. We do not sell personal information to any other organisations or companies, including those related to us. We will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others without first obtaining your consent, unless required to do so by law. 

We may monitor this website (including using 'cookies') in order to identify user trends, which will assist us in improving the site. If that occurs, the information will only be used in aggregate form and your individual details will not be identified or disclosed to any person. 

**User Registration (personal profiles)**

During free registration process users are required to provide their name and valid e-mail address. All information you provide during registration process and / or update information in your profile is confidential unless you make your profiles public. All this information is considered as "personal information".

**'This Site' uses cookies**

We use cookies to keep track of our registered members and/or visitors, and their activities. If you are unable to use the cookies, you will have to turn them ON in your browser setting in order to login and use members area. A "cookie" is a data file that is placed in your computer "temporary internet files". 

**Unlawful Activities**

'This Site' reserves the right to co-operate with local, provincial, national and international authorities in investigations of improper or unlawful activities and this may require the disclosure of personal information. We may also report to other organizations about improper or unlawful user activities on this website and this reporting may include disclosure of personal information relating to those individuals conducting such improper or unlawful activities.
